Coming into the sanuk.
We're going to be doing first the back of the leg massage.
There's a nice little comfortable way to come into this because I'm going to have a leg underneath her hip.
So first I'm going to fold up this leg closest to me.
I'm going to lift up the knee, change hands, steady myself, as I lift I'm rolling underneath her.
I'm going to do a rolling pin on the back of the legs.
So literally just roll the back of the legs with the rolling pin arms.
Back and forth.
This feels really nice.
It's not too hard.
It's not too gentle.
You can feel the muscles in the back of the leg releasing, relaxing the more you do it.
Going up and down as many times as you need to feel that relaxation coming into your client.
And then to come out of this you pick up, pick up, steady yourself, and just release the leg down.